How many lands of adventure are there, Dad?
我们在这里有多少个陆地要探险啊  爸爸
As many as you can imagine.
你想要多少就有多少
Which one are we going to first?
我们先从哪个开始呢
When are we going to get there?
我们什么时候能够到达那里
Will there be food? I'm hungry!
那里有东西吃吗  我饿了
Are we getting close? I'm thirsty.
快到了吗  我渴了
Please children, be patient!
孩子们  耐心点
Celeste, remind me next time we go on an adventure with the children-no children.
Celeste  记得提醒我  下次我们一起和孩子们探险时  不要再带孩子
Haha... Now dear...
哈哈哈  现在  亲爱的
Land! Land ahoy!
陆地  陆地  喂
Let me see!
让我看看
No! I'm first!
不 我要第一个
No! I am!
不  我来
Wow! Mom! Dad! I see an island!
哇  妈妈  爸爸  我看到了一个小岛
And I believe our first adventure is about to start!
我相信我们探险的第一个岛已经开始了
Uh oh!
不好